{
    "id": "1d047b7d9efd48d5b593d5de563d6205",
    "title": "Do vs. Have | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f48e7b04b6e14040870ab3e0d7e07f88",
            "title": "Do vs. Have",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………….. not have a car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………………….. my breakfast.",
                    "description": "I have had my breakfast means the same as I have eaten my breakfast. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "done",
                        "did",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………………….. never apologized to anyone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… not recognize him.",
                    "description": "Has and have are followed by the third form of the verb. Do, does and did are followed by the first form of the verb. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The guests ………………………….. all gone.",
                    "description": "Guests is a plural subject hence we use have with it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………….. hypocrites.",
                    "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "do not like",
                        "does not like",
                        "have not liked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where …………………………… she work?",
                    "description": "Use does with singular subjects. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ………………………….. she do to make a living?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where …………………………….. you hide the money?",
                    "description": "Do, does and did are followed by the first form of the infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where …………………………… he gone?",
                    "description": "Use has with singular subjects.",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "have",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………………….. no right to use my belongings.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "do",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}